Avi Gill

J 778-708-7131

dootrex 🕠

Vancouver, BC avigill@hotmail.ca

Portfolio: avigill.ca

Your friendly neighborhood Full Stack Developer

I am a self-motivated team player who has been working in team leader/supervisor roles for many years. I excel at learning new skills, problem-solving and motivating individuals. I am always looking for new challenges, experiences, and learning opportunities.

Skills: Javascript HTML CSS React NodeJS ExpressJS OAuth RESTful API Redux

Projects

emaily

An easy way to send surveys and have responses organized.

JavaScript, Redux, React, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, Sendgrid, Express

stock

infinite-bayou-69373.herokuapp.com/ github.com/dootrex/stock

A virtual Stock Trading Platform

Redux, React, JavaScript, HTML, CSS, NodeJS, Express, MongoDB

Education

Open Source Society University github.com

Mar 2020 to Sep 2020

Computer Science

Javascript: The Advanced Concepts | Udemy udemy.com

Jun 2020 to Jul 2020

Certificate, Computer Science

Full Stack Web Development | Udemy udemy.com

Apr 2020 to May 2020

Certificate, Computer Science

Simon Fraser University

Sep 2013 to Jun 2019

Bachelor's of Science, Physical Geography

Experience

Gateway Casinos Apr 2016 to Oct 2019

Poker Supervisor Burnaby, BC

Gateway Casinos Apr 2014 to Oct 2016

Table Game Dealer Burnaby, BC